SHRAVANI GUNAVANTH

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

408-887-2441 SGUNA002@ODU.EDU https://linkedin.com/in/sh rayanigunayanth

SUMMARY

Highly motivated and detail-oriented graduate with strong academic background in research and analysis, coupled with excellent interpersonal and organizational skills. Over 4 years of software development experience, specializing in designing, developing, and deploying both web-based and Client-Server business applications utilizing OOP and Java/J2EE technologies in a variety of industries including Finance, Health and Commerce.

SKILLS

C, C++,Java, Spring Boot, Python, CI/CD pipeline, Angular, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Github, REST API, Postman

EDUCATION

Old Dominion University

2023-Present

Masters in Computer

Science

Osmania University
2015-2019
Bachelors in Computer
Science

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer at JPMC **2021-2023**

Worked on a development of dashboard from scratch using Spring boot and Angular. Also worked on rest API's and developing new features in UI. Forr making REST API calls to the backend, I have developed Angular services using resource service. Successfully created and maintained automated CI/CD pipelines for code deployment using Jenkins while automating the deployment process, resulting in the elimination of 70% of manual work and escalation of work efficiency.

Software Engineer at NCR corporation

2019-2021

Worked on design and development of new features in the UI of application using C# .net. Worked on application security and identifying and fixing issues with SQL Injection, Script Injection, XSS, and CSRF attacks. Skilled in working on vulnerability tracking tools. Proficient in performing application security risk assessments throughout the SDLC cycle. Worked on a Software Distribution tool which manages to create a software package that can be delivered to terminals and manages the installation of those packages. Worked on developing complex SQL queries involving multiple tables and optimizing database performance.